[word "Remembering"] slides right 9px into place, ease-in, progressive reveal
[words "is", "so"] slide left 32px + fade in, ease-out
[words "Remembering", "is", "so"] slide out left 28px, fading
[product demonstration]
[word "Meet"] pops in
[word "your"] slides left 7px into place, ease-in
É +2 more events
[word "Meet"] pops out
[word "your"] slides out left 274px
[words "notes", "app"] slide up 182px into place, ease-out
[words "app", "notes"] slide out left 159px, ease-out
É +2 more events
[words "second", "brain", "second", "brain"] slide out left 214px
[words "though", "oartner"] slide left 258px into place, ease-out
É +2 more events
[words "though", "thought", "oartner", "partner"] slide out down 47px
[words "thought", "partner"] slide down 20px into place
[product demonstration]
[words "Capture", "anything"] pop in
[words "Capture", "anything"] pop out
[product demonstration]
[words "Turn", "brain", "into", "dumps", "notes"] slide down 23px into place
[word "beautiful"] slides down 9px + fades in, ease-in
[words "Turn", "brain", "into", "dumps", "beautiful", "notes"] pop out
[product demonstration]
[words "Let", "Mem"] pop in
[words "Let", "Mem"] slide out left 121px, ease-out
É +2 more events
[word "notes"] pops in
[words "notes", "for"] slide left 57px into place, ease-out
É +2 more events
[word "notes"] slides out left 6px
[word "you"] slides left 22px + fades in
É +2 more events
[product demonstration]
[word "Te!"] slides left 12px into place
[word "Te!"] slides out left 12px, ease-out
É +3 more events
[word "Mem"] slides left 86px into place
[word "remembers"] slides up 18px + fades in, progressive reveal
[word "for"] slides down 13px into place, ease-in
É +3 more events
[word "remembers"] pops out
[word "you"] slides up 9px into place
[words "for", "you"] fade out
[product demonstration]
[word "Find"] slides left 104px into place, ease-out
[word "Find"] slides out right 7px
[product demonstration]
Ñ hard cut Ñ
[word "and"] pops in
[word "and"] slides out left 66px, ease-in
[word "and"] slides left 67px into place, ease-out
[word "recall"] slides left 7px + fades in, ease-in
[words "and", "recall"] fade out, ease-out
[word "everything"] slides right 9px + fades in, ease-out, progressive reveal
[word "everything"] slides out left 10px
[words "Mem", "Chat"] fade in, ease-in
[words "Mem", "Chat"] pop out
[product demonstration]
[words "I've", "created", "to-do", "list", "for", "you"] slide up 30px into place, ease-out
[words "I've", "created"] slide out right 31px, ease-in
É +2 more events
[words "list", "for", "you"] slide out left 30px, ease-in
É +4 more events
[word "and"] slides out right 9px
[words "of", "course"] pop out
É +2 more events
[words "Team", "Sharing"] slide out up 19px
[product demonstration]
[words "Not", "notes"] slide left 136px into place, progressive reveal
[words "another", "app"] slide left 70px + fade in, ease-out
[words "Not", "another", "notes", "app"] slide out up 21px, ease-in
É +2 more events
[word "Your"] slides right 18px + fades in
[word "go-to"] slides right 21px into place
[words "thought", "partner"] slide right 26px + fade in, ease-out
[word "partner"] fades out, ease-out
[words "Your", "go-to", "thought"] pop out
[product demonstration]